So as we, the first person we'll be inducted is Eugenia Stolarczyk and before
we call up the council general who's going to induct her we have one quick
thing while we have Olivia here.
She's going to play a very short song and let me tell you about this song. Do
not think, unless she's 12 years old and she got stage fright or something and
suddenly cut off this song.
The Polish people in the room will understand this. She's going to play
something called a halo.
Every Polish person knows it. Hang on, may I ask you section on Gary word so it
means safe areas gone and it cracked out Poland every hour on the hour they
play this halo facing the foreign directions of the compass and it knew they
broadcast it to the whole world.
Poland into the whole world and the story behind the halo is pretty cool.
European cities used to have gates around them to keep the conquering tribes
out so hundreds of years ago there was tribes trying to enter crack out and at
the highest part of the church, St. Mary's Church in the tower, one of the
guards of sentries saw the tribes coming in and he started playing the halo to
alert.
They were able to close the gates but while he was playing the halo he got
shocked that arrow in the throat. The song ends abruptly there.
So it's pretty cool. It's a legend. When Olivia ends abruptly, did I think, 12
year old kid? No, this is correct. So Olivia, if you would play the halo for us.
[Halo music]
[Applause]